Herb Staehr Collection ARC.0029
Library and Archives
- Series VI: Concert, Studio, and Television Recordings [RESTRICTED], circa 1960s-2000s
  - Subseries 2: DVD-Video, circa 1960s-2000s
    - McCartney, Paul
      - Various including Up Close, Wetten Das, Hey, Hey, It's Saturday, 1993 February-1993 March (Box 11, Object 117)
      - Blockbuster Pavilion, Charlotte, N.C., 1993 June (Box 11, Object 118)
      - Saturday Night Live rehearsals, 1993 (Box 11, Object 119)
    - McGuinn, Roger
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1977 July 23 (Box 11, Object 120)
      - Global News and Much Music Show; Atlanta, Georgia, 1991 February 12, 1991 April 3 (Box 11, Object 121)
    - McVie, Christine: The Video Album, LIve in Concert, 1984 (Box 11, Object 122)
    - Miller, Steve: Loreley, Germany; Blues in the 20th Century, 1983 August 20, 1992 (Box 11, Object 123)
    - Moody Blues
      - Kansas City, Kansas, 1986 (Box 11, Object 124)
      - Denver, Colorado, 1988 (Box 11, Object 125)
      - BBC-TV appearances, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Object 126)
      - The Omni, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990 July 25 (Box 11, Object 127)
      - Jones Beach, Long Island, New York, 1990 August 4 (Box 11, Object 128)
      - The Omni, Atlanta, Georgia, 1991 August 23 (Box 11, Object 129)
      - Jones Beach, Long Island, New York, 1991 August 30 (Box 11, Object 130)
      - Reno, Nevada, 1991 August (Box 11, Object 131)
      - Wang Center, Boston, Massachusetts [news clip]; Sunrise, Florida, 1991 December 9, 1991 December 14 (Box 11, Object 132)
    - Moore, Gary
      - Dortmund, Germany; Tube, 1982 December 18, 1983 (Box 11, Object 133)
      - Live in Ireland, 1984 December (Box 11, Object 133-134)
      - Sight and Sound; Stockholm, Sweden, 1986, 1987 April 25 (Box 11, Object 135)
      - Various including Montreux, Switzerland with Albert Collins and The Video Singles, 1989-1990, undated (Box 11, Object 136)
      - Munich, Germany with Albert Collins [private]; "Still Got the Blues" and "Shapes of Things" promos, 1990 May 17 and undated (Box 11, Object 137)
      - Evening of the Blues, 1990 (Box 11, Object 138)
      - Live Blues, London, England with B.B. King, 1992 (Box 11, Object 139)
    - Morrison, Van
      - Various including Rainbow Theater, London, England, Bremen, Germany, Saturday Night Live, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Object 140)
      - In Ireland, Dublin and Belfast, 1979 (Box 11, Object 141)
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1982 April 3 (Box 11, Object 142)
      - Festival Place, Cannes, France, 1984 January 26 (Box 11, Object 143)
    - Motels: Sony Video 45: Motels; Musikladen, Germany, 1984 (Box 11, Object 144)
    - Mountain: Palais Omnisport, Paris, France, 1985 July 9 (Box 11, Object 145)
    - Muddy Waters: various including Jazz for Fun and Rolling Hotel, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Object 146)
    - Myles, Alannah: "Black Velvet" promo, Diamond Club, Toronto, Canada, rehearsals with Robert Plant, 1989-1990, undated (Box 11, Object 147)
    - Nazareth: Zeche, Bochum, Germany, 1984 November 12 (Box 11, Object 148)
    - Nicks, Stevie
      - Roxy, Los Angeles, California with Bob Welch; In Concert; "I Can't Wait" promos, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Object 149)
      - US Festival, California, 1982 (Box 11, Object 150)
      - Saturday Night Live; Rock a Little; Wilshire Theater, Los Angeles, California, 1983, 1986, undated (Box 11, Object 151)
      - Various including Stevie Nicks and Friends, VH-1 Behind the Music; VH-1 Storytellers, 1990, undated (Box 12, Object 1)
    - Omar and the Howlers: Austin City Limits, 1988 (Box 12, Object 2)
    - Outlaws: Tower Theater, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1982 July (Box 12, Object 3)
    - Page, Jimmy
      - Syracuse, New York, 1988 November 4 (Box 12, Object 4)
      - Old Grey Whistle Test; Live in Arizona, 1988 (Box 12, Object 5)
    - Paul Butterfield Blues Band: various including Newport Festival, Woodstock Festival, Night of Red Hot Blues with B.B. King, 1987, undated (Box 12, Object 6)
    - Perkins, Carl: Carl Perkins and Friends - Blue Suede Shoes: A Rockabilly Session with Eric Clapton, George Harrison et al, 1985 October 21 (Box 12, Object 7)
    - Petty, Tom, and the Heartbreakers
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany; Music Box; Santa Monica, California, 1977 (Box 12, Object 8)
      - Midnight Special; Rock Goes to College; Westfalenhalle, Dortmund, Germany, 1978, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Object 9)
      - Iowa State Center, Ames, Iowa, 1990 February 19 (Box 12, Object 10)
      - Nassau Coliseum, Uniondale, New York, 1991 October 8 (Box 12, Object 11)
    - Pink Floyd
      - "In the Flesh" tour [misidentified as Vienna, Austria 1972]; Venice, Italy, 1977, 1989 July 15 (Box 12, Object 12)
      - Shine On; Knebworth Festival, 1989, 1990 June 30 (Box 12, Object 13)
    - Plant, Robert
      - Maple Leaf Gardens, Toronto, Canada, 1988 May 10 (Box 12, Object 14)
      - Atlantic Records 40th Anniversary Concert; Rehearsals with Allanah Myles; PBS Center Stage, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 12, Object 15)
    - Police
      - Rock Goes to College; Top of the Pops; Bermen, Germany, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Object 16)
      - Markethalle, Hamburg, Germany; Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1980 January 11, 1980 October 18 (Box 12, Object 17)
    - Pretenders: various including Top of the Pops, Fridays, US Festival, Detroit, Michigan, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Object 18-19)
    - Quattro, Suzie: various including Top of the Pops, Live in Japan, Gas Tank, 1973-1983 (Box 12, Object 20)
    - Rainbow
      - Young Music Show, undated (Box 12, Object 21)
      - Rockpalast, Munich, Germany, 1977 October (Box 12, Object 21-22)
      - Live Between the Eyes, San Antonio, Texas, 1982 (Box 12, Object 22)
      - The Final Cut studio and live, 1985 (Box 12, Object 23)
      - Rockpalast, Philipshalle, Dusseldorf, Germany, 1995 October (Box 12, Object 24)
    - Rodgers, Paul
      - Tonight Show with Buddy Guy; Woodstock '94 with Slash; Rock Life, Cologne, Germany, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Object 25)
      - Rockpalast, Loreley, Germany, 1995 August (Box 12, Object 26)
    - Rolling Stones
      - Ed Sullivan Show, 1964-1969 (Box 14, Object 16, Box 10, Object 52)
      - Some Girls promos, 1978 (Box 14, Object 16)
      - Astrodome, Houston, Texas, 1981 (Box 12, Object 27)
      - Ohne Maulkorb, Vienna, Austria; Wembley Stadium, London, England, 1982 (Box 12, Object 28)
      - First 20 Years, circa 1984 (Box 12, Object 29)
      - Old Grey Whistle Test; La Saga Du Rock, 1986 (Box 12, Object 30)
      - Toronto, Canada, 1989 September 4 (Box 12, Object 31)
      - Coliseum, Los Angeles, California with Eric Clapton, 1989 October 19 (Box 12, Object 32-33)
      - Atlantic City, New Jersey and pre-show interviews, 1989 December 19 (Box 12, Object 34-35)
      - Tokyo Dome, Japan, 1990 February 26 (Box 12, Object 36)
      - Olympic Stadium, Barcelona, Spain, 1990 June (Box 12, Object 37)
      - Joe Robbie Stadium, Miami, Florida, 1994 November 25 (Box 12, Object 38-39)
      - Various including Voodoo Lounge interviews and rehearsals and 60 Minutes, 1994 (Box 12, Object 39)
      - St. Louis, Missouri, 1997 December (Box 12, Object 40-41)
      - Super Bowl XL halftime show, 2006 February 5 (Box 12, Object 42)
    - Ronstadt, Linda
      - Atlanta, Georgia, 1973 (Box 12, Object 43)
      - London, England, 1976 November 13 (Box 12, Object 44)
      - Seattle, Washington, 1976 (Box 12, Object 45)
      - New York, New York, 2004 June 1 (Box 12, Object 46)
      - In concert, undated (Box 12, Object 47)
    - Roxy Music
      - Various including Bremen, Germany, Stockholm, Sweden, Rock-Pop in Concert, 1973-1976, 1980 and undated (Box 12, Object 48)
      - High Road, 1982 (Box 12, Object 49)
    - Rundgren, Todd: Rockpalast, Germany, 1977 January (Box 12, Object 50)
    - Russell, Leon: Best of the Festivals, 1972 (Box 12, Object 51)
    - Santana
      - Hammersmith Odeon, London, England, 1976 December 15 (Box 12, Object 52)
      - Various including Winterland, Sydney, Australia, Live Aid, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1978-1985 (Box 12, Object 53)
      - Westfalenhalle, Dortmund, Germany; Pop-Rock, 1980 December 6 (Box 12, Object 54)
      - Palast der Republik, East Berlin, Germany, 1987 May 23 (Box 12, Object 55-56)
      - P.I.T., 1987 April (Box 12, Object 56)
      - Ohne Filter Extra, Baden Baden, Germany, 1987 (Box 12, Object 57)
      - Woodstock '94, 1994 August 14 (Box 12, Object 58)
    - Savoy Brown
      - Various including Black, White, and Blues -- 'Life is Too Short," and Oregon State Prison, 1972, 1987, undated (Box 12, Object 59)
      - Stone, San Francisco, California, 1987 (Box 12, Object 60)
      - Rainier Festival, Winthrop, Washington, 1989 (Box 12, Object 61)
    - Schrempf, Alvin
      - Eurosound Orchestra with members of Vienna Philharmonic, Austria, 2003 April 18 (Box 12, Object 62)
        Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
        PAL.
      - Glassart, undated (Box 12, Object 63)
    - Silver Wilburys [Taj Mahal, John Fogerty, Jesse Ed Davis, George Harrison, Bob Dylan]: Palamino Club, Los Angeles, California, 1988 (Box 12, Object 64)
    - Spirit: Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1978 March 4 (Box 12, Object 65)
    - Springfield, Dusty
      - Bravo profile, undated (Box 12, Object 66)
      - Full Circle, undated (Box 12, Object 67)
    - Starr, Ringo
      - Ognir Rrats with outtakes; Mike Douglas Show, 1978 (Box 12, Object 68-69)
      - Caveman, 1981 (Box 12, Object 70)
      - Buffalo, New York with All-Star Band, 1989 August 18 (Box 12, Object 71)
    - Stevens, Cat: Super Pop -- Montreux, undated (Box 14, Object 16)
    - Stewart, Al: Musikladen; Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1976, 1991 August 9 (Box 12, Object 72)
    - Stewart, Rod: Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 2007 February 21 (Box 12, Object 73-74)
    - Taylor, Mick
      - McGuffy's Draft House, Cleveland, Ohio, 1986 August (Box 12, Object 75)
      - Zeche, Bochum, Germany, 1989 April 17 (Box 12, Object 76)
      - Utah Blues Festival with John Mayall; Pistoia Blues Festival, Italy with Harman Bani, 1990 July 28, 1991 (Box 12, Object 77)
      - Diamond, Toronto, Canada, 1990 November 5 (Box 12, Object 78)
      - Scene Club, Vienna, Austria, 1990 (Box 12, Object 79)
    - Ten Years After
      - Sports Palace, Rome, Italy, 1968 May 6 (Box 12, Object 80)
      - Newport Jazz Festival, 1969 (Box 12, Object 81-82)
      - U.K. college rehearsals, 1969 (Box 12, Object 83)
      - Woodstock [NBC News Archives], 1969 (Box 12, Object 84)
      - Swing In / Rock In; When the Music's Over, 1969 and undated (Box 12, Object 85)
      - Various including Texas Pop Festival, Montreaux Jazz Festival, Isle of Wight Festival, Fillmore East, Woodstock, Beat Club, Bulk, 1969-1970; 1969-1991 and undated (Box 12, Object 86-92)
      - Various including Tucson, Arizona, Day in the Garden, Boston Music Hall, 1970-1974, 1998 (Box 12, Object 93-98)
      - Winterland Arena, San Francisco, California, 1975 August 4, 1978 May 19 (Box 12, Object 99-103)
      - Various including 16mm concert film, Ulm Festival, Germany with Frank Zappa, Old Grey Whistle Test, Marquee -- Woodchopper's Ball, Bulk, 1978-1979; 1978-1991, 2005 (Box 12, Object 104-109)
      - Graz, Austria, 1988 July 8 (Box 12, Object 110)
      - Milan, Italy; Jazz Festival, Frankfurt, Germany, 1988 July, 1991 December (Box 12, Object 111)
      - Nuremberg, Germany, 1988 August 7, 1992 (Box 12, Object 112)
      - Molson Park, Barrie, Ontario, Canada, 1988 August 27 (Box 12, Object 113-114)
      - Kurhalle, Vienna, Austria, 1988 December 1 (Box 12, Object 115-117)
      - Olympiahalle, Innsbruck, Austria; Neumarkt, Germany, 1998 December 2, 1988 December 18 (Box 12, Object 118)
      - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1989 November 12 (Box 12, Object 119-120)
      - Berlin, Germany; Munich, Germany, 1989 December 4, 1989 December 11 (Box 12, Object 121)
      - Frankfurt Jazz Festival; East Berlin, Germany; Rockhaus, Vienna, Austria, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Object 122)
      - Linz, Austria; Braunau, Austria; Peuerbach, Austria, 1990 March 20-1990 September 8 (Box 12, Object 123)
      - CA-Zelt, Vienna, Austria, 1990 November 3 (Box 12, Object 124)
      - Bratislava, Czech and Slovak Federal Republic, 1991 April 29 (Box 12, Object 125)
      - Vienna, Austria, 1991 May 3-1991 May 4 (Box 12, Object 126-129)
      - Timelkam, Austria with Luky Schrempf Band, 1991 May 5 (Box 12, Object 130)
      - Lorsch, Germany, 1991 August 25 (Box 12, Object 131-133)
      - Rockhaus, Vienna, Austria, 1991 November 15 (Box 12, Object 134)
      - Joselfhaus, Weiden, Germany, 1991 November 19 (Box 12, Object 135)
      - Heimathaus, Twist, Germany, 2002 August 28 (Box 12, Object 136)
      - Burg Clam, Austria, 2003 June 18 (Box 12, Object 137-138)
      - Seagarden, Reit im Winkel, Bayern, Germany, 2003 August 2 (Box 12, Object 139-140)
      - Regensberg, Germany, 2004 June 6 (Box 12, Object 141-143)
      - Legends of Rock Festival, Wiesen, Austria, 2004 August 6 (Box 12, Object 144-145)
      - Burg Clam, Austria, 2005 July 2 (Box 12, Object 146)
      - Regensburg, Schwandorf, Germany with Canned Heat and Iron Butterfly, 2005 July 8 (Box 12, Object 147-148)
      - Rockpalast, Herzberg, Germany; La Isla del Blues, 2005 July 16, 2005 September 19 (Box 12, Object 149)
      - Rockpalast, 2005 August 22 (Box 12, Object 150)
      - Lovely Days Festival, St. Pölten, Austria, 2006 July 21 (Box 12, Object 151-152)
      - 2005 (Box 12, Object 153)
      - Murzzuschlag Stadtsaal, Steiermark, Germany, 2006 April 29 (Box 12, Object 154-155)
      - Komma, Wörgl-Tirol, Austria, 2006 May 26 (Box 12, Object 156, Box 13, Object 1-2)
      - Jazz 'N' Blues, Rapperswil, Switzerland, 2006 July 1 (Box 13, Object 3-5)
      - Cannery, Las Vegas, Nevada, 2006 August 19 (Box 13, Object 6-8)
      - Sellersville, Pennsylvania, 2007 May 23 (Box 12, Object 9-12)
      - Altlengbach, Austria, 2007 June 1 (Box 13, Object 13-15)
      - Lovely Days Festival, St. Pölten, Austria, 2007 July 6 (Box 13, Object 16-18)
      - B.B. King's Blues Club, New York, New York, 2007 July 11 (Box 13, Object 19-22)
      - IMAC Theater, Huntington, New York, 2007 July 20 (Box 13, Object 23)
      - Magic Blues Festival, 2007 August 9 (Box 13, Object 24)
      - Heitere Open Air Festival, Zofingen, Switzerland, 2007 August 10 (Box 13, Object 25)
      - Posthof, Linz, Austria, 2007 October 11 (Box 13, Object 26-27)
      - Video history, undated (Box 13, Object 28)
    - Ten Years Later: Rock-Pop In Concert, 1979 (Box 11, Object 102)
    - Thin Lizzy: various including Top of the Pops, Australia with Gary Moore, The Tube, 1978 (Box 13, Object 29)
    - Thorogood, George: various including Rock Goes to College, Austin City Limits, MTV Rock Influences: The Blues, 1978-1986, 1995 (Box 13, Object 30-31)
    - Toler Brothers Band: State Theater, St. Petersburg, Florida, 1991 April 27 (Box 13, Object 32)
    - Traffic: Woodstock '94, 1994 August 14 (Box 13, Object 33)
    - Trower, Robin
      - Winterland, San Francisco, California; Midnight Special, 1975 (Box 13, Object 34)
      - Rock Goes to College; Night of the Guitars II, 1980, 1991 (Box 13, Object 35)
      - Rock & Roll Heaven, Toronto, Canada, 1986 (Box 13, Object 36)
    - Various
      - ABC In Concert: Grand Funk Rail Road, Freddie King, Allman Brothers, Chuck Berry, Poco, 1973 (Box 13, Object 37)
      - Action into Research for Multiple Sclerosis (A.R.M.S.) Concert, Forum, Los Angeles, California, 1983 December 9 (Box 13, Object 38-39)
      - All My Loving by Tony Palmer, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Object 40-43)
      - All You Need is Love
        - Seventies Glitter and Blues, undated (Box 13, Object 44)
        - Sixties, undated (Box 13, Object 45)
      - American Bandstand
        - 40th Anniversary Special, 1992 May (Box 13, Object 46)
        - 33 1/3 Celebration, undated (Box 13, Object 47-48)
        - Dick Clark's Golden Greats, undated (Box 13, Object 48)
      - American Idol, 2007 (Box 13, Object 49)
      - Atlantic Records 40th Anniversary Concert, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1988 May 14 (Box 13, Object 50-52)
      - Atlantic Records Story, 1994 May (Box 13, Object 53)
      - Beat Club
        - British Invasion, undated (Box 13, Object 54-55)
        - Compilation, undated (Box 13, Object 56)
        - Frontiers of Progressive Rock; Crazy World, undated (Box 13, Object 57)
        - Golden Big Hits; California Calling, undated (Box 13, Object 58)
        - Guitar Heroes; Revolution of Hard Rock, undated (Box 13, Object 59)
        - Jazz Rock; American Rock, undated (Box 13, Object 60)
        - Musikladen, undated (Box 13, Object 61)
        - Rebroadcasts, 1968, undated (Box 13, Object 62)
      - Beat! Beat! Beat!
        - 1967 January 20 (Box 13, Object 63)
        - Various including Move, Tony Sheridan, Small Faces, Pink Floyd, Procol Harum, Jimi Hendrix, Grateful Dead, Freddie and the Dreamers, Yardbirds, Cat Stevens, Helen Shapiro, Kinks, Peter and Gordon, Spencer Davis Group, undated (Box 13, Object 64-66)
      - "Best," Arena Kanagawa, Yokohama, Japan with Joe Walsh, John Entwhistle, Keith Emerson, Jeff Baxter, Simon Phillips, Rick Livingstone, 1990 September 26 (Box 13, Object 67)
      - Born to Rock: The T.A.M.I. / T.N.T. Show, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Object 68)
      - Bridge Benefit [Bill Graham tribute] with Crosby, Stills, Nash, and Young, Grateful Dead, Joan Baez, 1991 (Box 13, Object 69)
      - British and German television clips, undated (Box 13, Object 70)
      - California Screamin' (Box 13, Object 71-72)
      - Chronicle "The Beatles to Boy George" [see Super Night of Rock and Roll], 1984 February (Box 14, Object 33)
      - Cincinnati Pop Festival: Midsummer Rock, undated (Box 13, Object 73)
      - Cool Cats: 25 Years of Rock and Roll Style, undated (Box 13, Object 74)
      - Crossroads Festival, Bridgeview, Illinois, 2007 July 28 (Box 13, Object 75-79)
      - Don Kirshner's Rock Concert
        - Big Ticket Concert rebroadcast with Rolling Stones, Doobie Brothers, Earth, Wind, and Fire, 1973 (Box 13, Object 80)
        - VH-1 rebroadcasts with Eagles, Gladys Knight, Linda Ronstadt, Black Oak Arkansas, Leon Redbone, Steve Miller, Rasberries, Ike and Tina Turner, undated (Box 13, Object 81-82)
      - Ed Sullivan Show
        - Very Best of Ed Sullivan, 1991 February 17 (Box 13, Object 83)
        - Best of Ed Sullivan, Volume 2, undated (Box 13, Object 84)
        - Various including "British Invasion," "San Francisco Sound," "Tops Hits of 1968", undated (Box 13, Object 85-86)
        - Various including Jackson 5, B. B. King, Animals, undated (Box 7, Object 128)
        - VH-1 rebroadcasts, undated (Box 13, Object 87-88)
      - Fillmore, 1972 (Box 13, Object 89)
      - Fillmore East, undated
        - Mountain, Tommy Bolin and Zephyr, Ten Years After, Jethro Tull, undated (Box 13, Object 90)
        - Welcome to the Fillmore East, 1970 September 23 (Box 13, Object 91)
      - From the Bitter End (Box 13, Object 92-94)
      - Girl Groups: The Story of a Sound, 1983 (Box 13, Object 95)
      - Golden Age of Rock and Roll
        - Folk Rock; Great Performances, undated (Box 13, Object 96)
        - Male Vocal Groups; Hard Rock, undated (Box 13, Object 97)
        - Rock Guitarists; British Invasion, undated (Box 13, Object 98)
        - Rockabilly Beat; Havin' a Party, undated (Box 13, Object 99)
        - Sweet Soul Music; Legendary Ladies, undated (Box 13, Object 100)
      - Guitar Greats -- MTV Rockmentary, 1989 (Box 13, Object 101)
      - Guitar Greats Concert, Capitol Theater, Passaic, New Jersey with Dave Edmunds, Brian Setzer, Lita Ford, Neil Schoen, Tommy Iommi, David Gilmour, Johnny Winter, 1984 (Box 13, Object 102)
      - Guitar Men (Box 13, Object 101)
      - Heroes of Rock & Roll, undated (Box 13, Object 103)
      - Holland Music Festival: Stamping Ground, 1972 and 1983 (Box 13, Object 104)
      - Hollywood A Go-Go, Best of, undated (Box 13, Object 105)
      - International Rock Music Awards, 1989 (Box 13, Object 106)
      - Island Records All Star Story, hosted by Grace Jones with Free, Steve Winwood, Bob Marley, Eric Clapton, Robert Palmer, Roxy Music, Cat Stevens, U2, undated (Box 13, Object 107)
      - It Was Twenty Years Ago Today, 1987 (Box 13, Object 108-109)
      - Jools' Hootenanny with rehearsals, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Object 110-112)
      - "Ladies and Their Bands" -- television compilation, undated (Box 13, Object 113)
      - Live Aid, Wembley Area, London, England and JFK Stadium, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1985 July 13 (Box 13, Object 114-117)
      - Live from Greenwich Village
        - Volume 2: Neil Diamond, Odetta, The Happenings, Peaches & Herb, Tom Rush, undated (Box 13, Object 118)
        - Volume 3: Chad Mitchell and John Denver, Country Joe & the Fish, Paul Anka, Joe Williams, Dee Dee Warwick, undated (Box 13, Object 119)
        - Volume 4: Kenny Rogers and First Edition, Melanie, Chubby Checker, Marvin Gaye, Spanky and Our Gang, Tom Rush, Linda Ronstadt and Stone Poneys, undated (Box 13, Object 120)
        - Volume 5: Linda Ronstadt and Stone Poneys, Staple Singers, Box Tops, Jim Kweskin with Maria Muldaur, Kenny Rankin, Nina Simone, Gloria Tracey, Marvin Gaye, undated (Box 13, Object 121)
        - Volume 6: Mitch Ryder and the Detroit Wheels, Simon Sisters, Chuck Berry, Miriam Makeba, Orpheus, Candy Men, Sabicus, Staple Singers, undated (Box 13, Object 122)
        - Volume 7: "Interviews and Comedy Routines" with Woody Allen, Stiller and Meara, Dudley Moore, Red Foxx, Dick Cavett, Flip Wilson, Ron Carey, David Steinberg, Dustin Hoffman, undated (Box 13, Object 123)
      - Memphis Talent Party, undated (Box 13, Object 119)
      - Midnight Special
        - Compilation including Beach Boys, Blondie, Roger McGuinn, Clark and Hillman, Chuck Berry, Jerry Lee Lewis, Bobby Davis, Electric Light Orchestra, John Denver, Linda Ronstadt, Argent, undated (Box 13, Object 120-122)
        - Episode 44 with Procol Harum, Humble Pie, Alvin Lee and Mylon LeFevre, Steeleye Span, undated (Box 13, Object 123-124)
        - VH-1 rebroadcast with Loggins and Messina, Gladys Knight, O'Jays, Jim Croce, Al Green, Joe Cocker, Peter Frampton, undated (Box 13, Object 125-126)
      - Murray The K –- It's What's Happening, Baby, 1965 June 28 (Box 13, Object 127)
      - Music Scene compilation with Jerry Lee Lewis, Janis Joplin, Ten Years After, Joe Cocker, Everly Brothers, John Mayall, B.B. King, Beatles, James Brown, Crosby, Stills, Nash, and Young, undated (Box 13, Object 128)
      - New Musical Express, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Object 129-132)
      - Newport Folk Festival: Festival by Murray Lerner, 1967 (Box 13, Object 133)
        Newport Folk Festival film.
      - Newport Pop Festival, Northridge, California with Jimi Hendrix, Byrds, Booker T. and the MG's, Rascals, Eric Burdon and War, 1969 June (Box 13, Object 134)
      - Night at the Family Dog, 1970 February 4 (Box 13, Object 135)
      - 1960s color promos with Who, Jeff Beck, Small Faces, Mothers of Invention, Doors, Beatles, undated (Box 13, Object 140)
      - Old Grey Whistle Test
        - Best of, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Object 136)
        - Compilation with Dire Straits, Roxy Music, Doobie Brothers, Jethro Tull, Freddie King, Roy Harper and Jimmy Page, Eagles, Lynyrd Skynyrd, undated (Box 13, Object 137)
      - Out of the Blacks, Into the Blues, 1971 (Box 13, Object 138)
      - Playboy After Dark, Best of, undated (Box 13, Object 139)
      - Popcorn, 1969 (Box 13, Object 140)
      - Ready, Steady, Go!, undated (Box 13, Object 141)
      - Randall's Island New York Pop Festival: Day the Music Died, 1970 (Box 13, Object 142)
      - Rock and Roll, Volume 1-10 -- PBS documentary, undated (Box 13, Object 143-147)
      - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Induction Ceremonies, 1988-1998, 2005 (Box 13, Object 148-152)